recon.com 2010-06-21

# Recon - Photo profiles for gay men

**We have created this policy to demonstrate our respect for your privacy. Please read it carefully before using this website as it concerns use of your personal information.**

**Interpretation**  
Headings do not form part of this policy and will not affect their interpretation. 

In these terms and conditions, "you" refers to the member and "we", "us" refers to T101 Limited. Recon is a network of associated websites ("the sites") owned and operated wholly by us and consists of the following URLs: 

recon.com, bikermen.com, worldgaymen.com, worldleathermen.com, maskedmen.com, clubmuscle.com, worldpunks.com, worldrubbermen.com, worldskins.com, worldsportskit.com, world-uniform.com, slave4master.com, bondagecontrol.com, suitedguys.com, worldfist.com, bootedmen.com, gaypiercing.com, inkedskin.com, bearvillage.com, footsexboys.com, gayfighter.com. 

**Registration under Data Protection Act 1998**  
We are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 (UK). We make no use of personal information other than as set out in this policy. Except as otherwise provided below, we will not use any personal or confidential information or disclose it to any third party, unless we are required to do so by law. 

**Automated information collection**  
Our web server automatically recognises the domain name and email address of each user of this website. We collect IP addresses as well as details of your browser type so we can deal with service problems we may also use it to deal with issues arising from breach of our terms and conditions of use of the sites. 

**Cookies**  
When you visit a Recon website we send one or more "cookies" - small files containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, you will be unable to login and use all features of Recon if your cookies are disabled.

**Uses of personal information**  
The personal information we collect may be used for the following purposes: 

  * for purposes of processing payment of membership fees; 
  * internal review for our own operational purposes; 
  * to assess effectiveness and improve the content of the sites including gathering broad demographic information; 
  * to customise the content and/or layout of its website for each individual member; 
  * to notify members about offers and updates to the services and products available on the sites - you can opt-in or opt-out of such communications at any time by editing your Contact Options/Email Notifications under the 'My Profile' section of the sites. 

We may need to share your information with our service providers and agents for these purposes. 

**Your personal data - IMPORTANT**  
We advise you not to post information that can identify you (directly or indirectly) in your profile. You need to be aware that if you choose to do so, it means that you are choosing to place your personal data in a worldwide environment where some jurisdictions do not have adequate laws to protect your data by European standards. 

**Opting in**  
By default, promotional email is not sent to you. You can change your mind and choose to receive promotional emails from us in the future by editing your Contact Options/Email Notifications under the 'My Profile' section of the sites - this will not affect our ability to contact you regarding changes in our terms of use or our privacy policy. 

**Unsolicited adverts from other members**  
Any unsolicited commercial communication or information sent or attached by other members is in breach of the terms and conditions of use of the sites so please help us by reporting it to us with as much information to help us identify the offending member as you can give. 

**Disclosures**  
We will not disclose any personal information to third parties except:

  * as required by law; 
  * to law enforcement agencies when required to do so by relevant legislation; 
  * to enable us to investigate any allegations of abuse of the sites by a member; 
  * to allow subsequent owners of our business to continue to operate this website and the business; 
  * to any parent, subsidiary, sister or joint venture company which agrees to observe this privacy policy. 

**Other websites**  
Our sites also contain links to other websites (other than the sites we own) which are outside our control and are not covered by this privacy policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. We are not responsible for their use of your personal information so please take care to read their terms before you disclose it. 

Information submitted by users to one of the sites may be replicated on our other sites. 

**Access right**  
You have a right to access the personal data held about you at any time. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please email us at admin@recon.com. 

**Security**  
We employ a number of security measures to help limit the loss, damage, misuse and defacement of information that we control. Information that is gathered by us is stored on our secure servers. These servers are held in a high-security location and access is limited to authorised personnel only. Physical and electronic keys are used to prevent access to the servers, along with photographic identity cards. In addition, the servers themselves are electronically secured with multiple passwords. 

Our payment-processing partner uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that information between yourself and their servers is encrypted; the purchasing system is secure and any information passed between your computer and the payment-processing computer cannot be read by anyone that happens to intercept it. 

Your personal address and payment details are collected for order processing only. Your card will be billed as one of the following 

  * WWW.RECON.COM
  * MC - T101.COM INFO@T101.COM 
  * NETBANX-RECON.COM 
  * WP-T101 LIMITED 

**Right to amend these terms**  
We may at any time revise the terms of this policy by posting changes on the sites. The continued use of this website after changes are posted constitutes your acceptance of the modified terms. If you choose not to accept the modified terms and you are a fee paying member, we will upon request return a fair proportion (related to the time left unexpired on your membership) of the membership fee. 

**Applicable laws**  
The terms of this policy are governed and construed in accordance with the laws of England. If any of the terms is held to be unlawful, void or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision will be deemed severable and will not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining terms. You agree to submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the English Courts. 

**Registered Company Address**  
The Company is registered in England, UK at: Avaland House, 110 London Road, Apsley, Hemel Hempstead, Herts, HP3 9SD, United Kingdom
